A Guide to the Commonwealth Fund records, Indexes, SG 1, Series 40 FA438
Rockefeller Archive Center
Commonwealth Fund records, Indexes, SG 1, Series 40
1920s-1970s
Rockefeller Archive Center
Commonwealth Fund
FA438
14.92 Cubic Feet 60 3x5 card boxes, 28 4x6 card file boxes, and 1 5x8 card file box
Scope and Contents
Index card files documenting early grants, public heath fellowships, and the English Mental Hygiene Program. Portions of these card files also document subject files, general files and rural hospitals.
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research.
- General Files - A-Com (Box 1)
- General Files - Coo-Gr (Box 2)
- General Files - H-Len (Box 3)
- General Files - Li-On (Box 4)
- General Files - P-Sn (Box 5)
- General Files - Sp-Wi (Box 6)
- File by author (Box 7)
- File by author (Box 8)
- File by author (Box 9)
- Appeal Classification (Box 10)
- Miscellaneous Appeal Matter - see States General (Box 11)
- Appeal File (Box 12)
- Appeal File (Box 13)
- Appeal File (Box 14)
- Regional Plan (Box 15)
- Regional Plan (Box 16)
- Subject Index - A-Ce (Box 16)
- Subejct Index - Coa-Lo (Box 17)
- Subject Index - M-S (Box 18)
- Subject Index - Se-Z (Box 19)
- Cards for Numbering Appeal, 1930 January-1958 (Box 19)
- Cards for Numbering Appeal, 1930 January-1958 (Box 20)
- Aa-Am (Box 20)
- Am-Bar (Box 21)
- Bas-Bra (Box 22)
- Bre-Cas (Box 23)
- Ce-Coa (Box 24)
- Col-Ct (Box 25)
- Cu-Dz (Box 26)
- Ea-Fk (Box 27)
- Fl-Gq (Box 28)
- Gra-Hem (Box 29)
- Hen-Hz (Box 30)
- I-Jz (Box 31)
- Jones-Lem (Box 32)
- Len-Mar (Box 33)
- Mas-Mil (Box 34)
- Mim-ND (Box 35)
- Ne-Pd (Box 36)
- Pa-Pq (Box 37)
- Pr-Rh (Box 38)
- Ri-Schn (Box 39)
- Scho-So (Box 40)
- Sp-Tg (Box 41)
- Th-V (Box 42)
- V-Wal (Box 43)
- Annual Reports - Alabama-New Mexico (Box 43)
- Annual Reports - Ohio - Foreign (Box 44)
- Turndowns, 1974 (Box 44)
- Turndowns, 1974 (Box 45)
- Annual Reports - Foreign Countries (Box 45)
- Annual Reports - Foreign Countires (Box 46)
- Index Card to Board Reports to 1947 - Keep as Resource Files (Box 46)
- Wam-WT (Box 47)
- Wv-Z (Box 48)
- Mental Hygiene Administration Library (Box 48)
- Mental Hygiene Administration Library (Box 49)
- Special Grants - Austria - Legal Research (Box 49)
- Special Grants - Austria - Legal Research and Ed Child Health (Box 50)
- English Mental Hygiene Public Health (Box 51)
- English Mental Hygiene Public Health (Box 52)
- Health Studies Publications (Box 52)
- Health Studies Publications (Box 53)
- Untitled (Box 54)
- Cancer Program (Box 55)
- Rural Hospitals - Old Hospital Budget (Box 55)
- Rural Hospitals - Old Hospital Budget (Box 56)
- Rural Hospital - Hospital Abstracts - A-Economics (Box 56)
- Rural Hospital - Hospital Abstracts - Economics-L (Box 57)
- Rural Hospital - Hospital Abstracts - Economics-L (Box 58)
- Rural Hospitals SPL Statistics (Box 58)
- Project Files - A-H (Box 59)
- Project Files - Har-PL (Box 60)
- Project Files - Q-XYZ (Box 61)
- Public Health Fellowships - A-B (Box 61)
- Public Health Fellowships - C-N (Box 62)
- Public Health Fellowships - O-XYZ (Box 63)
- Rural Hospitals SPL Statistics (Box 64)
- Rural Hospitals SPL Statistics (Box 65)
- Rural Hospitals SPL Statistics (Box 66)
- Appropriation Cards - Public Health (Box 67)
- Appropriation Cards - Public Health (Box 68)
- Appropriation Cards - Public Health (Box 69)
- Appropriation Cards - Public Health (Box 70)
- Grants - A-Bel-Bez (Box 71)
- Grants - Bi-Cas-Caz (Box 72)
- Grants - Ce-Ch- Dh (Box 73)
- Grants - Di-Ga (Box 74)
- Grants - Ge-Hoa-Hol (Box 75)
- Grants - Hom-Hoq-Kn (Box 76)
- Grants - Ko-McC (Box 77)
- Grants - McD-Na (Box 78)
- Grants - Ne-Pl (Box 79)
- Grants - Po-Sa (Box 80)
- Grants - Scha-Sy (Box 81)
- Grants - Ta-Wek (Box 82)
- Grants - Wel- Z (Box 83)
- Educational Research Legal Research (Box 83)
- Obsolete Files - A-C (Box 84)
- Obsolete Files - C-G (Box 85)
- Obsolete Files - H-L (Box 86)
- Obsolete Files - Mc-P (Box 87)
- Obsolete Files - Q-T (Box 88)
- Obsolete Files - U-Z (Box 89)